<Articles><Article doc_id="5001"><doc_id>5001</doc_id><title>PLM &lt;PLMA&gt; UNIT ENDS MERGER TALKS</title><body>PLM Cos Inc said its PLM Power Co unit broke off merger discussions with Sunlaw Energy Corp of Beverly Hills, Calif.     In January PLM Power entered into a letter of intent to negotiate a potential acquisition of Sunlaw, subject to substantial due diligence, the company said.     But it also said the two companies were not able to agree on mutually satisfactory final terms and conditions.  Reuter </body><topics>acq </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5002"><doc_id>5002</doc_id><title>COLOMBIA OPENS APRIL/MAY COFFEE REGISTRATIONS</title><body>Colombia opened coffee export registrations for April and May with the National Coffee Growers' Federation setting no limit, Gilberto Arango, president of the private exporters' association, said.     He told Reuters the decision not to put any limit responded to "new factors" which have emerged from recent International Coffee Organisation talks in London, where producers and consumers failed to agree on a re-introduction of export quotas.  Reuter </body><topics>coffee </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5003"><doc_id>5003</doc_id><title>USDA REPORTS 10.572 MLN ACRES IN CONSERVATION</title><body>The U.S. Agriculture Department has accepted 10,572,402 more acres of highly erodable cropland into the Conservation Reserve Program, USDA announced.     In the latest signup, farmers on 101,020 farms submitted bids on a total of 11,254,837 acres.     The accepted bids for annual rental payments ranged up to 90 dlrs per acre with an average of 51.17 dlrs per acre.     Land entered into the Conservation Reserve Program will be ineligible for farming for ten years and must be planted with permanent vegetative cover.     Producers enrolled 1,894,764 acres of corn base acreage in the conservation program to take advantage of a corn "bonus" rental payment that was offered by USDA.     The corn bonus, to be paid in generic comodity certificates, amounts to two dlrs per bushel, based on the ASCS program payment yield for corn, for each acre of corn based accepted into the reserve.     The state showing the biggest enrollment in the conservation program during this signup was Texas with approximately 1.225 mln acres, followed by Iowa with 1.030 mln acres, Minnesota with 890,000 acres, Montana 875,000 acres, and Kansas with 842,000 acres.     Other states showing big enrollment were Missouri with 646,000 acres, North Dakota with 588,000 acres, and Nebraska with 554,000 acres.     In the corn belt states of Illinois and Indiana, 217,000 acres and 116,000 acres respectively were enrolled.     Farm land signed up to date in the conservation program totals 19,488,587 acres. Bids on the previous signups ranged up to 90 dlrs per acre with an average of 45.52 dlrs.  Reuter </body><topics>grain corn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5004"><doc_id>5004</doc_id><title>BRAZIL DEBT POSES THORNY ISSUE FOR U.S. BANKS</title><body>CitiCorp &lt;CCI&gt; appears to be digging in its heels for tough negotiations over the billions of dollars in loans that Brazil owes to money center banks, Wall Street analysts said.     "I view it as pre-negotiation posturing," said analyst Carole Berger of Cyrus J. Lawrence Inc, referring to both Brazil and Citicorp. Brazil recently stopped paying interest on its commercial bank debt. Today, CitiCorp said its first quarter income would be reduced by 50 mln dlrs after tax if it lists the loans as non-performing status.     Citicorp filed an 8-K form with the Securities and Exchange Commission, indicating a material change in its financial situation. "Citicorp is saying you can't scare us with threats, we'll make your loans non-performing right now," Berger said.     The loans have to be treated as non-performing after 90 days without a payment. CitiCorp said only that the situation will be reviewed at the end of the current quarter.     Berger asserted that Brazil is doing its own politicking by talking to U.S. regulators and trying to drive a wedge between U.S. and European banks.     Analyst Lawrence Cohn of Merrill Lynch and Co said it is unlikely the situation will be resolved until the second half of this year.     "Ultimately the Brazilians are going to have to pay up on all the interest they owe," Cohn said. "The real issue is the rescheduling of debt terms.     Another question is whether or not the International Monetary Fund can help Brazil with a new austerity program.     Stocks of money center banks were mostly down fractions in late dealings. One trader most stocks in the group bounced off their lows by midday as investors took the news in stride.     Cohn said the bank stocks may be risky until numbers on non-performing loans are reported for each bank. But he said investors looking ahead six to 12 months might want to buy at present levels for the "tremendous fundamental values" in the group.     Analyst Robert Gordon of Shearson Lehman Brothers Inc said Manufacturers Hanover Corp &lt;MHC) has the greatest exposure to Brazilian loans of any New York bank, in terms of percentage of earnings. He said his only two recommendations currently among New York banks are J.P. Morgan and Co &lt;JPM&gt; and Bankers Trust Co &lt;BT&gt; which happen to have the least exposure.     Gordon said his positive opinion on J.P. Morgan and Bankers Trust was not merely a response to the fact that the two have lower exposure to Brazilian loans than other banks.      In fact he said there's a chance those banks could get more involved in the future. He noted that Morgan has already set up a brokerage subsidiary to deal in loans to less developed countries.     "I don't see any reason to change full year earnings estimates, said Frederick Meinke, analyst at E.F. Hutton Co. He thinks the confrontation with Brazil could end in a replay of a situation that occurred with Argentina in 1984 and 1985.     Meinke noted that in the case of Argentina the loans became non-accruing for a couple of quarters but then when the banks came to an agreement with Argentina all the back interest was paid. "What it did was distort the quarterly earnings pattern," he said.     He said in the case of Brazil write-offs of loans is a worst-case outcome which is highly unlikely. He noted that Brazil is a country with a diversified economy, going through some economic upheaval after the transition from a military to a civilian government.     "The countries of Latin America have too much debt relative to their ability to service it," said John Mason of Interstate Securities. "We've been fiddling around with these problems for five years and the hour is growing late."     He said up to now the banks have reduced their spreads, cut interest rates internally and extended maturities and none of these measures has been enough. He expects re-classification of as much as a third of the loans as non-accruing and he sees partial write downs of some loans.     Nevertheless Mason thinks the money center bank stocks  could be poised for a short term rally.     A spokesman at First Chicago Corp &lt;FNB&gt; said it is premature to put Brazil's loans on a cash basis. "It is our expectation that economic development will allow Brazil to meet its debt," a spokesman said.     Bankers Trust in New York said it would be premature to make a decision. Several other banks queried by Reuters said much the same thing.     A spokesman at Manufacturers Hanover noted that of 2.3 billion dlrs in loan exposure to Brazil only 1.3 billion is subject to Brazil's unilateral moratorium on repayment of interest.      Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5005"><doc_id>5005</doc_id><title>ROCKWELL &lt;ROK&gt; TO REPURCHASE MORE COMMON SHARES</title><body>Rockwell International Corp said its board has authorized extension of the company's 500 mln dlr stock repurchase program by an additional 500 mln dlrs.     Since the beginning of the present repurchase program in March 1986, Rockwell said, it has bought 10.4 mln shares for 461 mln dlrs. At present prices, it said, the program would reduce the presently outstanding 140 mln common shares by about seven pct. Since November 1983, the company has repurchased 18.1 mln shares for 672 mln dlrs, it said.     Rockwell said the stock will be repurchased through open market and private transactions.     Rockwell said the repurchased shares will be available for potential acquisitions, stock options, employee benefit programs, conversion of convertible securities and other purposes.     The company said, "We continue to view our repurchase program as an integral part of our long term goal of improving shareholder values."     Rockwell said the program "complements our aggressive program of support for the growth plans of our businesses with capital investments, product and research development resources, and acquisitions in support of our core businesses."     Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5006"><doc_id>5006</doc_id><title>VOGTLE NUCLEAR PLANT GETS FULL-POWER LICENSE</title><body>The Nuclear Regulatory Commission issued a full-power operating license for Unit 1 of the Vogtle Electric Generating Plant, said Southern Co &lt;SO&gt; unit Georgia Power, which is a co-owner of the plant.     Georgia Power said the license allows for completion of pre-operational testing, which will be followed by full-power operation. Unit 1 is scheduled to begin commerical operation by June one, it said.     The other co-owners of the plant are &lt;Olgethorpe Corp&gt;, the Municpal Electric Authority of Georgia and the city of Dalton.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5007"><doc_id>5007</doc_id><title>BRITISH AIRWAYS &lt;BAB&gt; TO FLY TO TOKYO NON-STOP</title><body>British Airways said the British government reached an agreement on new traffic rights with the Japanese government which clears the way for non-stop flights between London and Tokyo.     The flight is scheduled to cut across Siberia, shaving almost six hours off the previous flight path to 11-1/2 hours, British Airways said.     The trans-Siberian route is subject to approval by the USSR, British Airways added.     Under the agreement, British Airways said it will continue to leave Heathrow daily, but the new non-stop service will operate on Thursdays and Saturdays starting early June. The company said return flights will be on Fridays and Sundays.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5008"><doc_id>5008</doc_id><title>BRITAIN WANTS BANK REGULATION DEAL WITH JAPAN</title><body>Britain wants Japan to agree a timetable for work towards joint rules on capital adequacy for banks along the lines of a January outline agreement between the U.S and the U.K., Corporate Affairs Minister Michael Howard said.     Howard told a Nikkei conference on Tokyo financial markets, "I want to see an agreement between us on what progress is to be made and the rate at which it will happen."     Japanese vice-minister of finance for international affairs Toyoo Gyohten told the conference yesterday he was ready to discuss capital adequacy, but no negotiations were planned and he could not see how or when agreement would be reached.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5009"><doc_id>5009</doc_id><title>U.S. MEAT GROUP TO FILE TRADE COMPLAINTS</title><body>The American Meat Institute, AME, said it intended to ask the U.S. government to retaliate against a European Community meat inspection requirement.     AME President C. Manly Molpus also said the industry would file a petition challenging Korea's ban of U.S. meat products.     Molpus told a Senate Agriculture subcommittee that AME and other livestock and farm groups intended to file a petition under Section 301 of the General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade against an EC directive that, effective April 30, will require U.S. meat processing plants to comply fully with EC standards.     The meat industry will seek to have the U.S. government retaliate against EC and Korean exports if their complaints are upheld.  Reuter </body><topics>livestock carcass </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5010"><doc_id>5010</doc_id><title>COMMERCE BANCORP &lt;COBA&gt; FILES FOR OFFERING</title><body>Commerce Bancorp Inc said it has filed a registration statement with the Securities and Exchange Commission for a 575,000 share Series B cumulative preferred stock offering, including 75,000 shares to cover allotments.     Commerce said it and its banking subsidiaries will use the proceeds to support their planned growth and for general corporate purposes.     The bank holding company said each share of preferred stocks initially will be convertible into one share of Commerce common stock.     Commerce said the preferred shares will be priced at a range of 20-22 dlrs a share, with a proposed sale to the public commencing in early-to-mid April.     Commerce said Butcher and Singer Inc will be the offering's managing underwriter.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5011"><doc_id>5011</doc_id><title>ADIA SERVICES &lt;ADIA&gt; SELLS 500,000 SHARES</title><body>Adia Services Inc said it agreed to sell 500,000 shares of common stock to its principal stockholder, Adia S.A., at a price based on the current market price.     The sale will raise Adia S.A.'s ownership in the company to 74.7 pct from 72.7 pct, Adia said.     The company also said it intends to use proceeds from the stock sale to retire debt, for working capital and for general corporate purposes.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5012"><doc_id>5012</doc_id><title>MET-PRO CORP &lt;MPR&gt; TO PAY REGULAR DIVIDEND</title><body>Qtrly 15 cts vs 15 cts prior     Pay May Eight     Record April 24  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5013"><doc_id>5013</doc_id><title>AILEEN INC &lt;AEE&gt; 1SR QTR JAN 31 LOSS</title><body>Shr loss 30 cts vs loss 20 cts     Net loss 1,553,000 vs loss 1,031,000     Revs 10.0 mln vs 8,696,000  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5014"><doc_id>5014</doc_id><title>INT'L GAME TECHNOLOGY &lt;IGAM&gt; TO SELL DEBT</title><body>International Game Technology said it filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission a registration statement covering a 35 mln dlr issue of senior notes due 1995 and a 25 mln dlr issue of convertible senior subordinated debentures due 2002.     The company named Drexel Burnham Lambert Inc as sole manager of the offerings.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5015"><doc_id>5015</doc_id><title>WOLVERINE WORLD WIDE INC &lt;WWW&gt; 4TH QTR LOSS</title><body>Shr loss six cts vs profit 55 cts     Net loss 414,000 vs profit 3,936,000     Sales 109.4 mln vs 126.8 mln     Year     Shr loss 1.75 dlrs vs profit 55 cts     Net loss 12,589,000 vs profit 3,965,000     Sales 341.7 mln vs 389.5 mln     NOTE: Year results include 14.0 mln dlr restructuring charge in 2nd Qtr of 1986  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5016"><doc_id>5016</doc_id><title>MEAD &lt;MEA&gt; FILES 150 MLN DLR SHELF REGISTRATION</title><body>Mead Corp said it filed a shelf registration with the Securities and Exchange Commission covering potential debt securities offerings of up to 150 mln dlrs.     It said the underwriters for this offerings may include Smith Barney, Harris Upham and Co Inc, Goldman Sachs and Co and/or Salomon Brothers Inc.     Mead said proceeds will be used to retire short-term debt, a portion of which was incurred to finance part of the recent acquisitions of Ampad Corp and Zellerbach Distribution Group.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5017"><doc_id>5017</doc_id><title>U.S. EXPORTERS REPORT 122,000 TONNES CORN  SOLD TO MEXICO FOR 1986/87
</title><body /><topics>grain corn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5018"><doc_id>5018</doc_id><title>HURCO COMPANIES INC &lt;HURC&gt; FIRST QTR NET</title><body>Shr profit three cts vs loss 18 cts     Net profit 124,000 vs loss 370,000     Rev 11.3 mln vs 11.7 mln     Avg shares 3,673,000 vs 2,368,000  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5019"><doc_id>5019</doc_id><title>ALCIDE'S &lt;ALCD&gt; SHELF REGISTRATION EFFECTIVE</title><body>Alcide Corp said its shelf registration of 4,500,000 shares of common has been declared effective by the Securities and Exchange Commission.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5020"><doc_id>5020</doc_id><title>MAXTOR &lt;MXTR&gt; AGREES TO ACQUIRE U.S. DESIGN</title><body>Maxtor Corp and U.S. Design Corp &lt;USDC&gt;, said they reached definitive agreement covering the acquisition of U.S. Design by Maxtor.     They said the arrangement, which is subject to a number of conditions including U.S. Design shareholder approval, calls for Maxtor to issue 12 mln dlrs worth of its own common stock in exchange for all of U.S. Design.     The number of Maxtor shares to be issued will be determined by the average closing price of Maxtor stock over the 10 trading day period prior to the day the acquisition becomes effective, the companies also said.  Reuter </body><topics>acq </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5021"><doc_id>5021</doc_id><title>SHARED MEDICAL SYSTEMS CORP &lt;SMED&gt; SETS PAYOUT</title><body>Qtly div 18 cts vs 18 cts prior     Pay April 15     Record March 31  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5022"><doc_id>5022</doc_id><title>INTERNATIONAL LEASE FINANCE &lt;ILFC&gt; PICKS ENGINE</title><body>International Lease Finance Corp said it picked the CFM International CFM56-5 high bypass turbofan engine to power its three new Airbus Industries A320 aircraft.     International Lease said it is negotiating to buy up to 27 more A320s. Initial aircraft deliveries are planned for 1991, the company said.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5023"><doc_id>5023</doc_id><title>JWP &lt;JWP&gt; SELLS 30 MLN DLRS OF NOTES</title><body>JWP Inc said it sold 30 mln dlrs principal amount of its 9.25 pct senior notes due 1996 to certain institutional lenders.     The company said about 15 mln dlrs of the proceeds will be used to pay debt and the balance for general corporate purposes.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5024"><doc_id>5024</doc_id><title>S/P UPGRADES UNION CARBIDE CORP'S 1.2 BILLION DLRS OF DEBT
</title><body /><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5025"><doc_id>5025</doc_id><title>ELECTRICITE DE FRANCE SAYS IT WILL LAUNCH EURO-COMMERCIAL PAPER PROGRAM ON MONDAY
</title><body /><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5026"><doc_id>5026</doc_id><title>STORAGE TECH &lt;STK&gt; IN DISCUSSIONS WITH IRS</title><body>Storage Technology Corp said it is holding dicussions with the Internal Revenue Service that could end their dispute over the amount of back taxes owed by the company.     "We are currently pursuing discussions with the IRS that could lead to a final solution," Stephen G. Jerritts, president and chief operating officer said. "Simultaneously, we are taking all necessary actions to try to expedite the court appeal process, resolve these issues and allow final court approval of the plan of reorganization, by our target date of June 30, 1987," he said.     Last year, Storage Technology's bankruptcy court ruled that the company owed about 25 mln dlrs in taxes, an amount much lower than the IRS is seeking.     The IRS has appealed the court's decision.     Jerritts also said his company and &lt;Siemens AG&gt; of West Germany extended an agreement under which Storage Technology distributes a laser printer made by Siemens.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5027"><doc_id>5027</doc_id><title>U.S. EARLY MARCH CAR SALES OFF 2.2 PCT</title><body>Retail sales of new cars by U.S. automakers eased 2.2 pct in early March to the weakest levels since 1983, with industry giant General Motors Corp down 9.3 pct while Ford Motor Co and Chrysler Corp both had gains.     The decline by GM continued its trend of weaker sales since the beginning of the 1987 model year, which has forced the world's biggest corporation to cut its car production several times through temporary and permanent layoffs at various plants.     Consumer incentives apparently had some success, analysts said, as the seasonally adjusted annualized sales rate improved to 7.5 mln compared with about 7.0 mln in late February. The eight domestic carmakers sold 8.2 mln units during 1986.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5028"><doc_id>5028</doc_id><title>CAPITAL INVESTMENTS FORMS UNIT</title><body>&lt;Capital Investments Development Corp&gt; said it formed Bradford-Taylor Clearing House Inc, a unit that will compile mailing lists for use by the direct mail industry.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5029"><doc_id>5029</doc_id><title>WEIGH-TRONIX INC &lt;WGHT&gt; 4TH QTR NET</title><body>Shr 18 cts vs 16 cts     Net 348,298 vs 308,927     Sales 4,166,750 vs 3,740,970     Year     Shr 72 cts vs 52 cts     Net 1,409,867 vs 1,020,096     Sales 16.5 mln vs 15.0 mln     Avg shrs 1,974,529 vs 1,956,214  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5030"><doc_id>5030</doc_id><title>GOLDMAN SACHS GIVEN BOGUS EXXON BONDS IN TRADE</title><body>Goldman Sachs International Corp received forged bonds of a unit of Exxon Corp &lt;XON&gt; in a trade, a spokesman for Goldman Sachs and Co Inc said in a telephone conversation from New York.     He said the transaction left Goldman Sachs International with an exposure of about 2.2 mln dlrs but that it had insurance to cover the loss.     The spokesman was responding to an enquiry about an item in the London "Standard" newspaper, which said Goldman Sachs "is feared to be the victim of a new multi-million pound City scandal."     The newspaper also said, "The firm (Goldman Sachs) is believed to be the paying agent for some 900 bonds issued in the name of oil giant Exxon which were deposited at banks in Brussels and have now been found to be forgeries."     The spokesman said that the bonds were delivered to the firm by a man working on behalf of a third party. He said it wasn't until the bonds were cleared through Euro-clear (a major clearing house for the eurobond market) that it was discovered they were forgeries.     The spokesman also said he believed that the intermediary had been apprehended by police. However, a spokesman for the City of London police said he was unaware of such an arrest and could neither confirm nor deny it.     Last Friday, Exxon Corp said forgeries of a 20-year zero coupon euronote issued by its Exxon Capital Corp subsidiary have been discovered in the European market. It also said Morgan Guaranty Trust Co was the fiscal agent and paying agent and that Morgan, Euro-clear and Cedel (another major clearing system) and police in London and Brussels were investigating the case.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5031"><doc_id>5031</doc_id><title>U.S. MEAT GROUP TO FILE TRADE COMPLAINTS</title><body>The American Meat Institute, AME, said it intended to ask the U.S. government to retaliate against a European Community meat inspection requirement.     AME President C. Manly Molpus also said the industry would file a petition challenging Korea's ban of U.S. meat products.     Molpus told a Senate Agriculture subcommittee that AME and other livestock and farm groups intended to file a petition under Section 301 of the General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade against an EC directive that, effective April 30, will require U.S. meat processing plants to comply fully with EC standards.     Reuter </body><topics>livestock carcass </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5032"><doc_id>5032</doc_id><title>EDF TO LAUNCH EURO-CP PROGRAM MONDAY</title><body>&lt;Electricite de France&gt; (EdF) will make its first offering of Euro-commercial paper in the international market on Monday, EdF chief financial officer Daniel Lallier said in a telephone call from Paris.     The program was announced in late January and dealers expect the company will be pushing to maintain its ability to obtain some of the finest terms available in the international markets.     Lallier did not say how much would be offered, although he has noted that EDF would be cautious because it believes the market is still in its infancy. In January he said EdF may not issue more than 300 to 500 mln dlrs of paper this year.     EdF plans to oversee the program itself, with Goldman Sachs International Corp, Morgan Guaranty Ltd and Salomon Brothers International Ltd acting as dealers for the general program, which will be aimed at institutional and retail investors.     Union Bank of Switzerland will act as dealer for a specific program, which is aimed at smaller retail investors.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5033"><doc_id>5033</doc_id><title>CBT TRADERS SAY U.S. CONSERVATION SIGNUP NEUTRAL</title><body>The 11,254,837 acres of highly erodable farmland submitted to the U.S. Department of Agriculture for the conservation reserve program was within trade guesses of 10-12 mln and should have an overall neutral impact on grain and soybean prices Monday, grain traders said.     Farmers enrolled 1,894,764 acres of corn base acreage in the conservation program to take advantage of a corn bonus rental payment that was offered by the USDA, which may underpin new crop futures, they said.     New crop corn prices firmed earlier this week on ideas of a large sign-up in the program. But traders noted that the poor yielding acres being set-aside will result in only a modest decrease in final production figures, since farmers will concentrate on high yielding land.     Of a total 11,254,837 erodoble acres submitted, usda accepted 10,572,402 acres into the program at an average rental payment of 51.17 dlrs per acre.     Farm land signed up to date now totals 19,488,587 acres.  Reuter </body><topics>grain corn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5034"><doc_id>5034</doc_id><title>MONARCH AVALON INC &lt;MAHI&gt; 3RD QTR JAN 31 LOSS</title><body>Shr loss 11 cts vs profit four cts     Net loss 199,000 vs profit 81,000     Rev 1.9 mln vs 2.5 mln     Nine months     Shr loss 14 cts vs profit 15 cts     Net loss 261,000 vs profit 273,000     Rev 6.4 mln vs 7.6 mln     NOTE: Per share information adjusted for three-for-two stock split on January 31, 1986.  Reuter </body><topics>earn </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5035"><doc_id>5035</doc_id><title>B.C. RESOURCES HAS NEW 360 MLN DLR CREDIT LINE</title><body>British Columbia Resources Investment Corp said it successfully concluded refinancing negotiations with bankers for a new 360 mln dlr restructured credit facility.     The credit line will be in place for four years to March 31, 1991, but is extendable up to 10 years under certain circumstances which were not specified by the company.     B.C. Resources said subsidiaries Westar Timber and Westar Petroleum have settled revised lending agreements, but debt discussions regarding subsidiary Westar Mining are continuing.   Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5036"><doc_id>5036</doc_id><title>ARGENTINE DEBT TALKS DIFFICULT - CENTRAL BANK</title><body>Central Bank President Jose Luis Machinea said negotiations with creditor banks on Argentina's 30 billion dlr private sector foreign debt were difficult.     "There is considerable divergence with the banks. We must try to get them to lower the spreads," Machinea told Reuter.     He said negotiations with the steering committee for the country's creditor banks in New York would not end next week.     Machinea leaves for New York tomorrow with Treasury Secretary Mario Brodersohn to complete Argentina's team at negotiations with the steering committee for a 2.15 biilion dlr loan to see the country through 1987.     Machinea said Argentina had World Bank support. He said he and Economy Minister Juan Sourrouille had discussed Argentina's loan request with World Bank Vice-President David Knox, who is currently in Buenos Aires.     Argentina is aiming at four pct growth in 1987 and has said this target is not negotiable. It has indicated that it would not put payment of interest due on its foreign debt ahead of its growth target if the loan was not granted.     The United States and 12 other industrial nations granted Argentina a 500 mln dlr bridge which was received this week.     Talks on the 2.15 billion dlr lona began in January.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5037"><doc_id>5037</doc_id><title>U.S. PRODUCER ENERGY PRICES RISE IN FEBRUARY</title><body>Prices of wholesale finished energy goods in the U.S. rose 4.0 pct in February after a 9.8 pct rise in January, the Labor Department said.     The Producer Price Index for finished energy goods fell by 20.9 pct in the past 12 months.     Heating oil prices rose 3.0 pct in February after a 18.0 pct rise in January, the department said.     Gasoline prices rose by 5.5 pct last month after a 15.7 pct January rise, the department said. Natural gas prices rose 1.8 pct after a 4.2 pct rise in January.     Crude oil prices rose 4.4 pct in February, after a 19.7 pct January rise and were off 21.3 pct from the year ago level.  Reuter </body><topics>crude gas nat-gas wpi </topics></Article><Article doc_id="5038"><doc_id>5038</doc_id><title>UNION CARBIDE &lt;UK&gt; DEBT UPGRADED BY S/P</title><body>Standard and Poor's Corp said it upgraded 1.2 billion dlrs of debt of Union Carbide Corp and its affiliate, DCS Capital Corp.     Raised were the pair's senior debt to BB-plus from BB-minus. Union Carbide's subordinated debt was upgraded to BB-minus from B.     S and P said the action reflected several positive factors which emerged over the past year, including a better balance of supply and demand in the chemical industry. Union Carbide has also benefitted from the turnaround in foreign exchange rates and lower feedstock costs, the agency noted.     Standard and Poor's said the company's asset sales, and subsequent use of the proceeds for debt reduction, exceeded the corporate plan of a year ago.     The rating agency also pointed out that Union Carbide's successful refinancing of more than 2.5 billion dlrs of long-term debt has resulted in a substantially lower interest burden.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5039"><doc_id>5039</doc_id><title>U.S. EARLY MARCH CAR SALES OFF 2.2 PCT</title><body>Retail sales of new cars by U.S. automakers eased 2.2 pct in early March to the weakest levels since 1983, with industry giant General Motors Corp &lt;GM&gt; down 9.3 pct.     Ford Motor Co &lt;F&gt; and Chrysler Corp &lt;C&gt; both had gains.     The decline by GM continued its trend of weaker sales since the beginning of the 1987 model year, which has forced the world's biggest corporation to cut its car production several times through temporary and permanent layoffs at various plants.     Relatively weaker sales by all of the Detroit Big Three carmakers have compelled the companies to offer a string of sales incentives including cash rebates and below-market interest loans in an effort to reignite the market.     Incentives apparently had some success, analysts said, as the seasonally adjusted annualized sales rate improved to 7.5 mln compared with about 7.0 mln in late February. The eight domestic carmakers sold 8.2 mln units during 1986.     GM said its sales of domestic-built cars in the March 1-10 period declined to 97,487 from 104,952 a year ago while truck sales rose 14.4 pct to 40,131 from 35,081. There were eight selling days in each period.     Despite the lower car sales, the giant automaker had a bright spot as its Chevrolet division, which is launching a national sales campaign this month for its new Corsica and Beretta compact cars, was up almost 21 pct when only domestic-built cars were counted. GM's Buick division was also up, by 11.4 pct, while Cadillac was down 7.8 pct, Pontiac was off 10.8 pct and Oldsmobile plunged 41 pct.     GM also showed an improvement in its market share to 53.6 pct from 48.1 pct in late February, which analysts said was partly due to the increasing sales for the new Chevrolets.     Meanwhile, Ford said its car sales rose 5.9 pct to 50,407 compared with 47,592 a year ago while truck sales gained by 12.6 pct to 35,814 from 31,811.     Number three Chrysler's car sales gained to 0.4 pct to 25,286 from 25,191 while its truck sales gained 15 pct to 15,565 from 13,585. The truck sales were a record for the period, the company said.     Among the smaller makers, Honda &lt;HMC&gt; said domestic car sales rose 16 pct to 4,394 from 3,786 and Volkswagen of America rose 4.9 pct to 849 from 809.     American Motors Corp &lt;AMO&gt; fell 57 pct to 760 from 1,780 for cars but rose 18 pct in jeep sales to 4,500 from 3,800.     Nissan &lt;NSANY&gt; car sales rose 19.1 pct to 2,137 from 1,794 and gained 3.6 pct on trucks to 1,686 from 1,628. Toyota &lt;TOYOY&gt; said it sold 500 U.S.-built cars compared with none a year ago.  Reuter </body><topics /></Article><Article doc_id="5040"><doc_id>5040</doc_id><title>U.S. COTTON CERTIFICATE EXPIRATION DATE EXTENDED</title><body>Expiration dates on upland cotton certificates issued under the 1986 upland cotton program are being extended, the Agriculture Department announced.     The certificates are being extended because of a shortage of Commodity Credit Corporation inventory available for exchange with certificates, USDA undersecretary Danial Amstutz said.     Presently, upland cotton commodity certificates expire nine months from the last day of the month of issuance.     Under the new procedure, all current outstanding and all new upland cotton certificates issued under the 1986 upland cotton program will have an expiration date of either February 29, 1988, or nine months from the last day of the month in which the certificate is issued, whichever is later.  Reuter </body><topics>cotton </topics></Article></Articles>